

K M Frihim

Contact

Street Address

House # 08, Road # 12, Block # D, Section # 06, Mirpur, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Cell

+88-01722530810

E-mail

frihim.ist.cse@gmail.com

Top Skills

- PHP, MySQL
- · Javascript, jQuery, Ajax
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- · Laravel, Codeigniter, Restful Api

Professional Summary

Strong in design and integration problem-solving skills. Expert in PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Laravel, Codeigniter, Lumen with database analysis and design. Skilled in developing business plans, requirements specifications, user documentation, and architectural systems research. Strong written and verbal communications.

Work Experience

03/2019 To Present

AROLLO TECH LIMITED

House # 296, Lane # 04, Baridhara DOHS, Dhaka, Bangladesh.

Senior Software Developer

- Design and develop HR Assistance system
- Integration of Al Service
- Dialogue Flow Integration for chatbot
- Maintain the project using GCP.
- Access the application by Different social media.

11/2015 to 02/2019

ATI LIMITED

House # 01, Road # 09, Sector # 07, Uttara, Dhaka, Bangladesh Team Leader

- Develop and maintain ERP system for Pharmaceuticals company.
- Develop and maintain One stop shop solution For UNDP.
- Develop and maintain Crowed Funding project for UNDP.
- Develop and maintain Forest Inventory for FAO.
- Support and maintain Project Management and Information System.
- Mange team and contribute to SAP (System architecture and planing) team

06/2014 to 11/2015

UNIQUE WEBERS LIMITED

Web Application Developer

- Develop ERP Solution for small business.
- · Develop Inventory management system.
- Develop website using raw PHP and CMS

Education

2014-2015

Institute of Science & Technology

M.Sc in COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING

- Passing year : 2015
- · University: National University, Bangladesh

2009-2013

Institute of Science & Technology

B.Sc Honors in COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING

- Passing year: 2013
- University: National University, Bangladesh

2006-2008

GOVT. ASHEK MAHMUD COLLEGE, Jamalpur

Higher Secondary School Certificate Secondary School Certificate

Passing year : 2008Board : DhakaMajor : Science

2001-2006

POLISHA HIGH SCHOOL, Madarganj, Jamalpur

Secondary School Certificate
• Passing year : 2006
• Board : Dhaka
• Major : Science

Languages

Bangla — Native Speaker

English — Proficient

Reference

Mahbubur Rahman

 $Staff\ Research\ Engineer\ at\ Samsung\ Research\ America\ |\ Digital\ Health\ Email:mmrahman@memphis.edu$